Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[ENGINE IDLING. DOOR AJAR TONE
DINGING]
[EERIE MUSIC]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION AND
LAUGHTER]
Is that all he's got?
[ROLL-UP DOOR CLOSES]
Yeah. James has like
five belongings.
We still running
to Waffle House?
Absolutely not.
Looks like solitary
confinement up there. man.
Yeah. you need to get
some plants or something.
It's actually depressing.
Hey. I appreciate the car. T.
Ain't no problem. man.
Happy to help.
Not gonna to lie to you.
you look old as hell. man.
Y'all look about the same.
I think that's everything.
Hey. do I still have to pay
for food if you guys hardly
helped at all?
Duh.
That's crazy.
The way I know
you're not joking.
Yeah. no. I give you rats.
That is an auto-lock.
first round draft pick. OK.
but it is hawks in the two spot.
What?
Dude. that's an atrocious pick.
That's terrible.
You could kill a hawk
with your bare hands.
Dude. you cannot take
a fucking Hawk. OK?
That is a bird of prey.
It would carve your ass up.
You. uh. got work lined up?
Uh. no.
I'm still trying to get
my shit figured out.
Every bird has brittle
fucking paper bones.
There is not a
bird on Earth that
could survive a human uppercut.
There is a position that I'm
looking at for an internship.
It would push your shit in.
Hawks are a terrible pick.
It's gun guy in
the two. for sure.
It's for sure.
No.
Yo. Day. you gotta back me up.
You gotta back me up.
What am I backing up?
50 hawks. dude with the gun.
5 gorillas. 10.000 rats.
You're gonna pick
two to defend you
and you're gonna
pick two to hunt you.
[UPBEAT MUSIC]
This really what
y'all talk about now?
I guess.
Yeah. Tyler. get in here.
You know. just help me out.
Can you please settle this?
What's my options again?
All right. you got 50 Hawks.
10.000 rats. 5 gorillas.
and a guy with a gun.
So you're going to pick two to
defend you and two to hunt you.
So if you're stupid and
pick. like. let's say.
hawks and gorillas.
10.000 rats--
Oh. my God.
Oh. brother.
Is this the
first-day-of-work fit?
You're wearing a tie to work?
I love this.
This is genuinely amazing.
First Communion drip.
Yes.
I look funny.
You look so funny.
[CHUCKLES]
That is what I just said.
Oh. and look at the
little briefcase.
It's a normal-- it's just
a normal-sized satchel.
It's significantly smaller
than most briefcases.
Hey. man. I think
you look spiffy.
It actually looks like a purse.
And I think that gun guy
would take hawks all day.
No.
OK. you keep saying that gun
guy just. like. takes hawks.
But who-- OK. who's gun guy?
You have to define gun guy.
Just assume he's
the aggregate human.
He's like the average man.
OK.
What kind of gun?
Hunting rifle.
OK. so he's like a--
so he's a hunter?
No. he's the average.
He's the average man.
OK. then what-- who's
the average man?
Probably--
Dude.
--a Chinese guy in a coal mine--
OK.
--or like a Staples.
Yeah. see. neither one of
those guys is taking 50 hawks.
You're delusional.
They're not charging
you head on.
He can wait you out.
Ooh. can I give the
gorillas guns and then
have like five gun guys?
Let's go.
Valid.
I'm taking this serious.
Valid point.
That's my genuine--
--response to that question.
Hey. where am I at?
Oh. like. where do you spawn?
Good question.
No. dude. where am
I going right now?
Right in three miles.
Unless we're picking up
more stuff at his place.
No. thank you.
Next question.
James. your apartment is
literally four gray walls.
Yeah. dude. it feels like
the Unabomber's cabin.
You don't even have a table.
Can you be excited
about one thing?
Like. just for once?
Like. I wish I had my
own place to decorate.
Where are you headed. Day?
Uh. home for now.
Gotta get on my
ZipRecruiter grind. I guess.
What'd you study again?
Graphic design.
The backbone of the economy.
You know. you could always
go into prospecting.
I heard gold is huge right now.
Look at that.
Always got something
to say. right?
Always gotta input
something. that two cents is.
Regardless. I don't
need to decorate.
It'll be months before I
even see my coworkers as
like sentient beings.
much less invite them
over to see my rug or
rubber duvet or bullshit.
Fish. I was surprised you and
James didn't move in together.
man.
Ugh.
Oh.
[LAUGHS] I don't know
if that would work.
Oh. holy shit.
Tyler. you never
answered the question.
OK. I'll tell you what.
If it ends this
conversation. I guess
I'll go hawks and gorillas.
Yep. Tyler in clutch.
Tyler in clutch.
Air superiority.
I could take 50
hawks. no problem.
James. you cannot take 50 hawks.
You simply cannot.
Oh. but you can train
gorillas and give them rifles?
That's not-- that's not too far?
As a matter of
fact. yes. I could.
Who's that monkey-loving lady?
June--
Jane Goodall!
Jane Goodall. dude.
Jane Goodall.
Jane Goodall did not do that.
She did not do that.
Yes. she did.
Actually. though. biggest
Nobel snub of all time. though.
She didn't win the Nobel Prize?
Mnh-mnh.
Jane.
OK. fine.
I have no business knowing that.
Conversation over.
I could. though. for the record.
Yeah. there's no
record. actually.
Yeah. literally no record.
Oh. right here. T.
That Jane pull was crazy.
I know. right?
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
[POWERFUL WIND. SCRATCHING]
You sure about this turn. Day?
Uh. yeah.
It just says go
straight from here.
All right. what
about you. Tyler?
How are you doing. man?
How's the-- how's the
real world treating you?
I mean. the HVAC work's
pretty steady. but. uh--
Tell you one thing. I ain't
talked about gorillas and rats
and shit in quite a while.
Do you no longer meet
the day with glee. Tyler?
Wait. does your spirit no
longer yearn for adventure?
OK. satchel.
What's your big plan?
What. you still figuring it out?
I mean. network engineer's
starting salary is $70K.
Five to seven years.
I'll scale to $150.000.
Make safe investments.
move to some random fuck
city like Milwaukee. settle
down with my best option.
get into pottery
or some bullshit.
I'll then shovel wasted
potential in my first kid.
have a second with some
sort of physical deformity
because. you know.
aging sperm count.
I love how in your
made-up. horrible life
you still make six figures
and have a loving family.
You know. I think
I'd like to be put
into some sort of. like.
medically-induced coma.
Jesus Christ.
Hooked up to. like.
serotonin oxy cocktails
that are released via--
Oh. wah. wah.
--big fun buttons I press.
So that's the plan. huh?
No offense. T. Real life
seems like it sucks ass.
No offense.
I mean. sometimes it does. dude.
I mean. it can't be all bad.
How are things with
you and Hannah?
Wait. T. you in a thing?
Actually. Day. we. uh-- we
split up a few months ago.
Oh. shit. man.
What happened?
[SIGHS] Ah. you know. I'd
rather not get personal.
Oh.
Tyler. I'm begging you.
Please get personal.
I'm on my hands and
knees begging you.
Tyler. please.
[SIGHS] I met Hannah when
I was on leave from base.
We were seein' each
other bout five months.
and she asked me to get serious.
You know. at first. I thought.
it could be a thing. you know?
I like the chick. and
she liked me. too.
But she wanted me to--
she wanted me to--
She what?
What?
She wanted to meet
up and pick pumpkins.
What?
Like. she wanted me to
drive three hours up
to meet her and pick
pumpkins together.
I know. so what?
I mean. y'all asked
why it didn't work out.
[LAUGHS] Are you joking?
I thought you liked her.
No fucking way.
I don't know. man.
She wanted to pick
fucking pumpkins. man.
She wanted to go to an apple
yard. vineyard. fall activity
bullshit.
That's what ended your
relationship with a human being?
It wasn't just the
goddamn pumpkins. man.
It was the three-hour drive up.
No. no. no.
Man. fuck y'all. you know?
Like. I'm ready to
settle down. you know?
I'm not trying to
bullshit like that.
You're ready to
settle down. Tyler?
I mean. what the fuck
else am I gonna do?
Well. I'm sorry you had that.
you know. happen to yourself.
It's all good. man.
I mean. she moved on.
I'll move on too.
Tyler. I'll tell you
one thing. though.
What?
That new guy she's
with is definitely
somewhere picking fucking
pumpkins with her right now.
You're god damn right.
You know. I actually--
I actually took a girl
to a pumpkin patch once.
and it was a fantastic time.
Fisher. no offense. you're
exactly the kind of guy
to be at some apple
vineyard. pumpkin patch.
whatever the fuck
with your soul mate.
Probably wearing corduroy.
Dude. no. you're just
fucking on me today.
Like. how is that even
offensive that I--
I'm somewhat agreeable or--
Hey. I'm sorry.
Where's this turn at?
Did I miss it?
Uh. no. it just says
go straight from here.
We should be the goddamn
highway right now. man.
Something's wrong.
Sorry. did James distract you?
Are we fucking lost?
Says go straight. man.
Nah. I'm gonna hit a U-ey.
Dude. it says go straight.
Nah.
[WIND WHISTLING]
Yo.
You good?
What is this?
I'm sorry for ragging
on you earlier.
Is this self-awareness?
I wasn't apologizing.
I was just acknowledging
that I was ragging.
OK. yeah. there it goes.
Buh-bye.
Why are you so jumpy today?
It feels like you're like
breakdance fighting right now.
Yo. T. you good?
I wouldn't pass this
motherfucker. man.
Yo. T. slow down.
I didn't pass a goddamn turn.
Oh. shit.
Fuck!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[GROANS]
You good?
Yeah. I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Is everybody OK?
Oh. my God.
[SCOFFS]
Did-- did we miss the turn?
I'm sorry. I didn't--
I didn't see it coming.
Listen. Tyler. fuck Maps.
If there's a dead end. we passed
by our entrance on the way back.
Did we miss it twice?
It's fine.
We missed a turn.
Let's just turn back.
I didn't miss a turn.
Yeah. you did.
No. I didn't.
Guys. it's fine.
We missed a fucking turn.
How else would we
have hit a dead end?
This is where we came in at.
Dude. what the-- what the
fuck are you talking about?
What?
[ENGINE IDLING]
I didn't miss a fucking turn.
Tyler.
Yo. T. Yo. get back
in the car. man.
OK.
[HAZARD LIGHTS CLICKING]
Well--
Dude. why are you pressing him?
I'm not pressing him.
Yes. you are.
No. I'm not.
You made it serious. man.
Is vehicular
manslaughter not serious?
Yeah. but you're just.
like. being a dick about it.
OK.
My chest hurts.
I'm getting out.
You're first mad.
No. you're first mad.
Are you done with your
temper tantrum yet?
I want to leave.
Give him a sec.
I don't know why
he's so on tonight.
You know he's only acting like
that because Tyler is here.
He hasn't seen him
in so long. bro's
putting on the
performance of a lifetime.
And he's not gonna admit it.
but he's for sure gonna miss us.
Yeah.
What?
Dude. I don't know.
I feel like we did
only turn just once.
[WIND WHOOSHES]
Fisher!
[HORN ALARM BLARING]
What the fuck!
Oh. my God!
Aah!
[SCREAMING]
Let me in!
Please!
Help me!
Fisher!
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING AND
SCREAMING]
[HORN BLARING]
Wait!
[SCREAMING AND SHOUTING
CONTINUES]
Ah!
Get off me!
Fisher!
Day!
Oh. my God!
[SCREAMING AND SHOUTING
CONTINUES]
[TIRES SCREECHING. BODIES
THUDDING]
Fisher!
Fisher. talk to me.
[SCREAMING]
Fisher. talk to me!
Are you OK?
[SCREAMING]
[HORN HONKING]
[DOORS CLOSING]
[ENGINE REVS. TIRES SCREECH]
[MOANS] Fuck!
Fuck!
James. you got to stop
the bleeding. man.
Get something from
the fucking back!
Get us off this
fucking road right now!
Get off this fucking road!
What the fuck!
What the fuck was that!
A fucking group car jacking?
No. they weren't a team.
They were attacking each other!
They didn't attack me.
They didn't attack you!
Dude. what the fuck
are you saying?
They wanted the car.
OK. so clearly they didn't
want to be where the fuck
we are right now!
They were all running
from something?
Somewhere?
They were fucking scared!
Why were they fucking scared?
Why the fuck did
they want the car?
Listen out.
Listen out what just happened.
Listen out what we know. OK?
There's people in the woods.
They want the car.
What else?
Guys. the road!
I never made a turn
once I got on this road.
That's the fucking
way we came in.
That's our entrance. I promise.
So those trees just
fucking appeared!
The trees just fucking appeared!
That's what you're
fucking saying!
[DISSONANT MUSIC PLAYING]
Where's this fucking turn at?
I got nothing.
It hurts so fucking bad. dude.
Maybe it was a drug den.
Or maybe they were
like escapees?
Maybe they were just
waiting for other cars.
Gas is at a quarter tank.
[GRUNTS] Tyler.
Tyler. it's bleeding. man.
It's fucking-- it's
bleeding again.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
All right. let's stop and
get our bearings straight.
I can tie this tighter.
[SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
[WHIMPERS]
You gonna be all right. man.
Hey. hey.
Calm down. bro.
Gonna be all right.
It's just a fucking cut.
Hey.
You OK?
My chest is. like. throbbing.
It's better.
You good?
How's that?
Tighten it.
Yeah.
Is that too tight?
No. it's OK.
[THUD]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[ENGINE REVS. TIRES SCREECH]
What the fuck. man!
What the fuck!
[CRYING] What the fuck?
What the fuck?
How?
We were driving--
[PANTING]
Maybe we just didn't
drive far enough away.
They came from the side.
They came from the fucking side.
Doesn't matter where
they came from.
Got to keep driving anyways.
Just look out for the turn.
We don't know where
we are right now.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYS]
[TONE SOUNDS]
Hey. T. Is your
gas meter broken?
Wasn't yesterday.
It's bright enough we
can see in the woods.
Day. if you want to
pull over. I'll drive.
Right here.
Thanks.
Hey. wait. wait. wait.
Maybe. um-- Maybe
don't turn the car off.
Don't.
[ENGINE IDLING]
James. pop the hood.
[HOOD OPENS]
You guys hear anything?
Still no signal.
Dude. I don't know of
any roads that drive
for six hours with no turns.
I don't know how or what--
I know.
This car shouldn't be running.
Fish.
Guys.
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING AND
SCREAMING IN DISTANCE]
Hey.
Everybody get in the car!
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING CONTINUES
IN DISTANCE]
But--
What-- what-- what the fuck is--
what the fuck is this place?
Um-- Yeah. this is not. uh--
this is not real life anymore.
No. this-- I mean. look. the
people. the dead end. the gas.
the fucking car
is still working--
What the fuck are you saying?
James?
My brain immediately goes to
some sort of. like. lucid dream.
but I've never done that.
Let's just start
from the top then.
I mean. what were we doing?
We were-- we were unpacking
and then-- and then
we were just talking.
And then we hit this dead end.
So. you know. maybe we crashed?
You know?
The driving. the
road-- maybe you
keep doing what you were
doing when you died.
I did not kill us.
Don't put that shit on me.
I am not saying
that you killed us.
I'm saying that you crashed.
James. do not blame him.
Don't fucking blame him. OK?
We never crashed.
Look. I'm not mad
if he killed us.
I'm just trying to process. OK?
Saying we're dead
is not processing.
It kind of is now.
This is not real life.
OK. so then what?
How does that change
our situation?
I don't know. which is why
I'm trying to talk about it!
Stop fucking yelling at me!
OK?
I'm gonna fucking freak.
I'm gonna freak out.
We need a practical answer.
We don't need to be worried
about what or why caused this.
I am being practical.
I mean. what the fuck else
is there to do besides drive?
If there are still people in
the woods. every time we stop.
someone needs to sleep
so we can take shifts.
Just-- we cannot stop moving.
I'm good to keep going.
I got more hours than me.
If we do stop. we
don't turn the car off.
Do not touch the key.
Pull over. swap.
get back in. go.
OK.
OK. look. we're not in
the right state of mind
to be dealing with
this right now.
so we keep driving for
the rest of the day
while we can still
look for an exit.
And then--
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[STATIC CRACKING]
Dude. I-- [BREATHING SHALLOWLY]
I can't sleep.
I can't-- I can't
fucking sleep. dude.
Like. I can't turn
my fucking brain off.
I can't fucking sleep either.
It's like I'm not even--
I'm not even tired.
24 hours later and I'm not--
not even hungry.
Yeah. I'm sorry.
guys. but there's no--
there's no turn coming.
James. you really
think we're dead?
I mean. it's definitely
on the table.
Yeah.
Well. you seem to be
handling it pretty well.
So just this?
Forever?
Why the fuck would
this be the afterlife?
I mean. it doesn't have
to be the afterlife.
You know. it could be--
you know. it could be anything.
Like what?
I don't know. like a drug trip
or like a wormhole or like a.
you know. ancient
curse we triggered.
You think we might
have caused this?
Like something we did?
I mean. look. not to--
not to point fingers. but did
anyone do anything horrible
recently?
You know. something.
like. evil--
that would curse us?
No?
No one wants to confess that
they. like. drunk-drove and hit
a small child?
Like this is some ironic
driving punishment?
Tyler?
Question was sort of
positioned at you?
Fuck off.
I haven't done anything
to deserve this.
Dude. none of us have.
OK. fine.
Any other guesses?
Seriously.
Group brainstorm here.
Anything goes.
I don't know. I was kind of
thinking this felt like--
like maybe purgatory?
OK.
Purgatory.
So let's start there.
How do you escape purgatory?
I don't know. it feels
like you have to--
you have to. like.
repent or something.
or you'd have to be judged.
I can't remember.
Shit. dude. I fucking--
Fuck. man.
I never-- I never
should have told my mom
I wasn't religious anymore.
This is fucking me up. dude.
If she thought that I was
dead. she would genuinely
believe that I am in Hell.
She would totally-- it
would ruin her fucking life.
We don't even know
that we're dead yet.
so they wouldn't think that.
They just think we're--
I don't know. missing.
Or we might actually be in hell.
So you could-- you can give your
parents. you know. some props.
You are un-fucking-believable.
Do you guys think
we deserve this?
No.
Personally. no.
I mean. I'm not perfect.
but this definitely
seems like overkill.
OK. I might have.
you know. a sin.
Fuck. you know. school was
getting too much on top of work.
which felt fucking
pointless because I
had to go back home for my
little sister anyway. but--
may have tried to.
you know. kill myself.
Day--
OK. can we. like. fucking relax?
James. is this not what
you wanted to talk about?
Why didn't you-- why
didn't you tell us?
That's insane.
I don't fucking know. Fish.
You would have just
tried to tell my parents.
and James would have just
tried to fucking philosophy me
or weaponize it.
Hey. whoa. what the fuck?
Look. I only brought it
up 'cause I thought maybe
we'd all done it.
Like. maybe that's
why we're here.
Well. fuck me then. I guess.
No. Day. you don't have to--
Don't say that.
It's fine.
Actually emotional catharsis
or sharing secrets.
that's a great idea.
Is anyone here carrying
a big weight. you know.
something that's maybe
specifically between us?
Tyler?
I mean. you seem like you
got something going on.
I'm the most well-adjusted
person in the vehicle.
No offense. Day.
None taken.
Agreed.
I mean. it was nice getting
to see you all again and--
I don't think I did
anything that would
have caused us to end up here.
But I don't think worrying
about if I did or not is
gonna change anything either.
I mean. this is--
this is above us.
But you never killed
anyone. right?
I never fucking deployed. man.
James. you don't think that
there's anything that you
might have done. you know?
I mean. maybe I took
my life for granted
or I didn't commit to
the right deity. but--
Fish. you are genuinely
my best friend.
Day. I'm sorry I wasn't
there for you last year.
Tyler. I missed you. man.
Thank you guys for
being my friends.
I love you guys.
Fuck. I thought
that would do it.
Well. maybe if you
actually meant it. then--
I did mean it.
Are you telling me I
went soft for nothing?
Yeah. maybe it's a
forest full of people
James has been a dick to.
That would explain
why we're here.
Maybe it's a forest full of
people I've given dick to.
It would be a barren forest.
I definitely wouldn't
fucking be here.
How long do y'all
think we can do this?
Just sitting in here.
driving all day.
I mean. what else can we do?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYS]
[HORN HONKING STACCATO]
[HORN HONK SUSTAINED]
[ENGINE IDLING]
There.
What the fuck?
[SHOUTING AND SCREAMING IN
DISTANCE]
James.
[ENGINE REVS. TIRES SCREECH]
About a minute 30.
OK.
A minute 30 to
explore the woods.
All right. then.
When the sun comes
up. I'll go in.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYS]
[DOOR AJAR TONE DINGING]
[HAZARD LIGHTS CLICKING]
[BRUSH RUSTLING]
[PANTING]
[HORN HONKING]
[DOOR AJAR TONE DINGING. HAZARD
LIGHTS CLICKING]
[TIMER RINGS]
[ENGINE REVS. TIRES SCREECH]
I could only make
it 100 yards out.
Nothing but woods.
There's still people out
there just laying there.
OK. 640. static.
[STATIC CRACKLING]
650. static.
670. static.
[TIMER RINGS]
Come on. T. Come on.
T. Let's go. man.
Tyler. come on.
Tyler.
OK. guys. we've got flashlight.
Tyler's spare clothes. phones.
anything that's already
downloaded on them.
Charger.
Car manual.
And also this Clif Bar.
What happens if
we eat something?
Yeah. no. probably
shouldn't eat that.
Could be digesting that forever.
[ENGINE IDLING]
30 seconds. guys.
Getting tired at
the same number.
I'm not building any muscle.
Everything's just too specific.
It just feels like designed.
I'm not getting tired.
I'm not hungry.
No sexual arousal.
I'm guessing.
James. please.
This is supposed to
be my alone time.
OK. but I'm healing normally.
Right. but he's still healing.
[TIMER RINGS]
15 seconds.
We got to go.
Fuck.
If see this again. it's a loop.
Are we going clockwise?
Yeah. clockwise.
[GROANS]
[TIMER RINGS]
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING AND
SCREAMING IN DISTANCE]
[PANTING]
[TIMER RINGS]
Tyler. let's go.
Come on.
90 seconds.
Come on. come on.
Where are we. man?
Where the fuck are we at. man?
What the fuck is this place?
Say something. God damn it!
Where are we?
Where the fuck are we at. man?
[HORN HONKING]
[SCREAMING] Help me!
Help me!
[TIMER RINGS]
We got to go. man.
Let's go.
[MAN SCREAMING IN DISTANCE]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TIMER RINGING]
Yeah.
Guys--
What's wrong?
I'm just. uh-- you
know. another--
[WHIMPERS]
It's OK.
Another panic-- dude--
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I want to be unconscious.
I want to go to bed.
I want to sleep.
You know?
I want to go home.
What is this for?
Why is this fucking happening?
This is-- I don't
want to be in here.
I want to get out.
It's OK.
It's all right.
I want to get out
of the fucking car.
What the-- what
the fuck did we do?
[WHIMPERS] Dude.
Fuck.
Fish?
Oh. shit.
Day. start the timer.
We should talk to them.
How?
We don't need to talk to them.
Don't get out of
the fucking car.
Do not get out of the fucking.
I'm not getting out of the car.
What the fuck do we need
to talk to them for. man?
They could have answers.
Answers?
If we pull this fucking car up
and they cut us off. we're done.
We have to drive regardless.
We're not turning around.
If we turn around on the road
right now. we can wait them out.
You're saying that
they're bad guys?
We cannot afford
to lose this car.
We're coming up on a minute.
We to make a decision now.
No one's saying anything
about losing the car.
We don't even know what this is.
All we know is that
this is something new.
This isn't a fucking
puzzle. dude.
This is our goddamn lives.
Get back in the fucking car!
Tyler. do something!
We need to get him!
Tyler. drive!
[INAUDIBLE]
[PANTING]
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
James.
What is it?
The odometer is past a million.
How many years of
driving is that?
[TIMER RINGS]
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING AND
SCREAMING IN DISTANCE]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[ENGINE REVVING FASTER]
Tyler. what are you doing?
Tyler.
Slow down. Tyler.
Tyler. what are you doing?
Tyler. stop.
Tyler. please!
Slow the car down.
Stop!
Stop doing this!
Slow down. Tyler!
Please. stop!
Tyler. please!
Stop the car!
Please. Tyler!
Stop it!
I'm sorry!
Tyler. Tyler.
Tyler. please!
Please. Tyler. stop!
I'm sorry!
[ENGINE REVVING SLOWS]
[SHIFTS GEAR]
[ENGINE IDLING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[WIND BLOWING]
[SILENCE]
[ENGINE IDLING]
All right. what
do you want to do?
What do you want to do?
What do you think
happens after the panic?
Like. once the car's
gone. what happens?
I don't know. they
probably returned to. like.
dormancy or something.
T?
Tyler.
What the fuck?
I can't sit in that
metal box and worry. man.
Can't keep worrying about
shit that don't end.
Worry?
Tyler. it's-- it's
not worry. man.
It's-- we're-- we're
figuring it out.
I don't really give
a shit what it is.
I'm not doing it no more.
Like. years of this shit?
I'm not living my life
in 90-second breaks.
Just tell them it wasn't for me.
What the fuck are you
even gonna do out here?
I don't know.
Is that it?
You're not gonna try to
talk me into staying?
You excited about the leg room?
[TIMER RINGS]
[HORN HONKING. ENGINE REVVING]
Let me know if you find an end.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Dude--
What the fuck?
Where is Tyler?
Dude. pull up. pull
up. pull up. pull up.
Move!
Day--
Tyler!
James.
Where is he?
I'll tell you--
What are you doing?
What is this?
What the fuck happened!
Where is he?
Day. we've gotta go.
You gotta get in
the fucking car.
I don't give a shit.
Where is Tyler?
Day. please.
Say something.
Get in the car!
Day. please get in the car.
Get in the fucking car!
Day. get in the car. please!
Day. please. get
in the fucking car.
Tyler!
Day. we gotta go!
Get in the car!
Come on. let's go!
Drive. drive. drive!
Go. go. go. go. go!
[TENSE MUSIC BUILDING]
What the fuck happened!
What-- what happened?
He gave up.
[MUSIC CRESCENDOS]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[RUMBLING]
Dude. the sun is
so fucking weird.
Dude. shut up.
Shut the fuck up.
Shut up!
We get one song.
You were doing so good.
You have to be quiet
for three minutes.
Just pick another.
Absolutely not.
We have to save them.
[MID-TEMPO POP MUSIC PLAYING]
(SINGING) So. it's on
The feeling's gone and moving on
Time is only mine to steal
Working on what is real
Found my song
Sang it wrong. no fooling
Warming up to all my chills
Thinking I'm over the hill
Tell me not to dwell
'cause I don't feel
like no one else. oh
OK. guys. warm up over.
It's 8 o'clock.
Good morning. good morning.
Good morning.
All right. James. start us off.
Um. gloves.
Like.
Big like.
Dislike.
Why do you dislike gloves?
Don't trust them.
Suspicious.
OK. windshield wipers.
Oh. hard pass.
What do you have against
windshield wipers?
Big dislike.
I do not understand why they
need more than one speed.
You just look goofy. OK?
You're on a highway. right?
Right.
Light rain.
You see-- you look
over and you see a guy.
and he still can't see.
You look insane.
Dude. I will
raw-dog a hurricane.
I'm like a torpedo.
I don't even see the water.
You're absurd.
Oh. OK.
Oceans.
Oh. absolutely not.
Absolutely not.
Dislike.
Nope.
Not for me.
Why don't you like the ocean?
Imagine living in a place where
you have to sprint 24/7 so that
something 50 times your
size doesn't demolish you.
Like. our species
was born in water.
and it was so fucking
horrible that we grew legs
to get out of it.
Yeah. all right.
I. like. agree with that.
Oh. I think we're gonna have to
pause "like and dislike" time.
We've got a green Honda.
One point.
You don't get a point.
That's beige.
It's not a beige car.
That's khakis on wheels.
That's not khakis on wheels.
[ENGINE IDLING]
[TIMER RINGS]
[WHISTLES] Time to go.
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING AND
SCREAMING IN DISTANCE]
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
Man. I'm getting good.
Just give me a
couple more months.
I'm gonna be fluent.
Oh. totally. man.
Yeah.
You realize your
Spanish is gonna
be heavily car related. right?
Watch this.
[SPEAKING FLUENT SPANISH]
OK.
Mr. Bilingual.
You know what we should do?
We should learn Spanish
just so we can communicate
without James understanding.
Terrific idea.
I second that.
I will learn it out of spite.
It's almost 10:00.
I'm checking out for
a bit before my shift.
You know. you could definitely
learn another language. man.
It's really good stimuli.
You know what I'm thinking?
I was this fucking close to
downloading Subway Surfers
before we turned up to
the stupid fucking road.
Where were we going?
Where were we going that day?
I don't know.
I legit can't remember.
Tyler was helping us
move out of college.
He came up a day early to
hang out and get food with us.
so we were going out.
Oh. yeah.
Do you think eventually we'll
have talked about everything
ever. and just never have
any new stimuli ever again?
Wait. dude.
Look at that.
[CHUCKLES] Wait. wait. wait.
Check out this gas I
cooked up last night. man.
I never shoulda smoked dat shit.
Now I'm on the endless road.
[LAUGHS] Me on the endless road.
Like. this one.
Me when people come
out of the woods.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Dude. asphalt companies
be like. "big ups."
[LAUGHS] Big ups. Big ups.
James be like.
"where's this turn at?"
That's funny. yeah.
I'm looking at these
and I'm realizing.
like. I barely have any
photos of my family in here.
Just like a bunch of
meaningless bullshit.
Saturated photos of the
Geico lizard shitting.
Hey. it's noon.
[CHUCKLES]
[ENGINE IDLING]
[SCREAMING]
[LAUGHS]
I want to eat this.
I want to eat this
so bad. y'all.
Like. I don't even
care what happens.
I just want to taste something.
No.
Part of our original items.
Here for a reason.
Talked about this.
Do you hear yourself?
It's a Clif Bar.
[TIMER RINGS]
Air-out time.
All right. I will start.
Start your engines.
Can I start?
Yes.
OK. uh. James. I know
this isn't Six Flags.
but can you please
be a little more
positive during our routine.
I think it would really
benefit you to just.
you know. scream and let
it out with us just once.
Fair.
Day. you're overattentive
to my emotions
and it's annoying as fuck.
Yeah.
Fair.
I can stand to be more patient.
Um. I think designated
music time is bullshit
and I should just listen
to music whenever I want.
so we shouldn't do it anymore.
Fair.
No.
You can't just say no.
Day. you were driving
with your legs up today.
Can you not do that? 'Cause
you're gonna crash us.
OK. fair.
But I literally won't.
That's ridiculous.
Fair.
But you're ADHD as
fuck. and yes. you will.
Fair.
James. stop psychoanalyzing
me all the time.
Fair.
But I'm not though.
Yes. you are.
Fair.
Fisher. you're soft as baby
shit and you take things
too personally.
Unfair.
Why are you so pressed
all the damn time?
We're trying to have--
You're just gonna attack
my person and then--
Fair.
Day. Fish is not
your little brother.
Oh. blow me.
You have negative drip.
and you get no bitches.
and you fucking stick.
You're musty. and there
are no bitches to get.
[TIMER RINGS]
What's next on the schedule?
My favorite part of the day.
[MID TEMPO POP MUSIC PLAYING
FROM EARLIER] Wait. no.
You got your shirt.
It's a simple hop.
1. 2. 3. 4. 5. 6. 7. 8.
That's literally it.
That's all you have to do.
It's so easy.
That's it.
Please.
Please do it.
All right.
What a surprise.
[TIMER RINGS]
Every time we get through the
second act. it's like somebody--
I mean. next time.
Help me!
(MOCKINGLY) Help me!
[LAUGHS]
Somebody help me!
[BOTH RIFFING INDISTINCTLY]
Story time.
Who's up?
James?
Oh. I have one.
It's pretty good.
All right. let's hear it. man.
It's actually about Tyler.
When he got suspended.
Oh. shit.
Was that senior year?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
OK.
Go. go. go. go.
Tell us.
Right as school ended.
Tyler went across the street
to the gas station.
That's literally right across
the street from school.
And he's in there loading up
on like $80 worth of vapes
and Smirnoff with his fake ID.
And while he's in there. Coach
Shive. Miss Ingle. and Mr.
Govreau. they all walk
in at the same time.
And obviously there's
three teachers there.
and they confront him
at the counter. right?
And they're like. "give us
your fucking fake." right?
And he's in deep shit.
The manager is
behind the counter
getting ready to call
the fucking cops.
And Coach Shive is
disciplining him
so that he doesn't get arrested.
And so then Tyler
literally just says--
he says. "oh. you know what?
Uh. I have more fakes in my car.
I'm sorry. but I'll
just go get them."
He walks out of the gas station.
he just gets in his car.
and he just fucking dips.
Dude. no fucking way.
He dips.
He's gone.
Yeah.
And so he goes to
school the next day
and he's in the parking lot.
and all of the principals
are waiting for him. right?
And they're like. "what the
fuck was that yesterday?"
Tyler literally just says-- he
just looks at them and goes.
"no. I didn't really want
to deal with it then."
Dude.
Yeah. that was it.
Yeah.
The guy's a legend.
I know He just walked out
of 7-Eleven being like.
"I just won."
And he did.
I mean. yeah.
He was probably so happy he
didn't have to go to school.
No. definitely.
Dude's crazy.
Yeah. it was good.
He won.
Do you guys think we could have
done something differently?
No.
He was a stubborn bastard.
Maybe one day we'll
go back for him.
Go back?
Yeah.
Go back.
Save him.
The answer is forward. Day.
The answer?
Yes.
James. what do you
think the road is?
I don't know.
I need to know more first.
No.
I know you've been thinking
about it for a long time.
So what do you think it is?
I don't know.
I'm just still learning.
What else is there to learn?
You know. why are
you even asking?
I'm only asking because
I know you still care.
And you don't?
I mean-- I mean. I'm here.
And so you just don't care
about any of this. then?
James. what are we doing?
We're making progress.
That's it.
OK. James.
OK.
[DOWN-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS]
Hey. honey.
I was just calling to
see how you're doing
and to see if you got
my package that I sent.
I couldn't find the kind
of peanut butter you like.
but I got a different kind.
I hope you like that.
Not much else has happened.
Uh. we did our routine.
Same as always.
James didn't scream
with us again.
I hope Mom is doing OK.
I hope you're doing OK too. sis.
Happy birthday!
Whoo!
Love you guys.
[MUFFLED SCREAMING]
[TIMER RINGS]
[ENGINE IDLING]
Hey. something's different.
No one.
Maybe less people
make it this far.
It must be his car.
Yo!
This your car?
[CLAPPING]
Yo!
Hello.
This is huge.
This is fucking huge.
I mean. there's no more people
trying to Grand Theft Auto us.
This means something.
Am I wrong?
Like what?
We made it past the scary part?
Look. there was a guy in
the woods. and he gave up.
We're continuing.
It feels like that
we're actually getting
closer to something here.
Yeah. man. we get it.
It's good.
There are people out there
that are giving up and losing
themselves.
That's what-- that's
what's gotten us farther
than most people out here.
It feels like that we're
actually moving towards a goal.
You know. I kind
of miss the feeling
that we first felt when
we first got on the road.
You know. that hope for a turn.
You know. I miss feeling
things in general.
Yeah. it's almost like--
like we're feeling weaker
shades of emotions that
used to feel really intense.
Guys. what the fuck is this?
What?
What the fuck is this?
This is a fucking
sign of something.
This is-- this is a new thing.
This is a good thing.
That's what it is.
That's the good thing. man.
I just--
Because it's new.
We haven't seen this before.
I think you should just be
careful about your. you know.
expectations and stuff.
What are you talking
about expectations?
I didn't say anything
about expectations.
This means something
absolutely brand new.
I mean. you're just
getting excited. man.
You should be careful.
It's not about me
getting excited.
Yes. it is.
It's not about me
getting excited.
You guys want to
talk about emotions?
Why the hell are you guys--
why the hell are you guys
getting so depressed then?
There's new information.
We can spend time
outside of the car.
It's nothing more than that.
We're literally just
trying to get you to be
a little bit more realistic.
I am completely neutral
about the situation.
Because if you have
these expectations.
you're going to be disappointed!
I don't fucking
have expectations!
Shut the fuck up. everybody. OK?
No anger in the fucking car!
[ENGINE IDLING]
Air-out time.
I'll go first.
James-- I think we
should stop driving.
I can drive.
What?
I know it sucks to have to work
out here. so I can take it--
always.
We don't have to divvy
up shifts anymore.
I'll take them all.
[ENGINE IDLING]
30 more minutes of outside time.
James-- uh. digest an entire
cylinder of PVC pipe or floss
every 15 minutes?
PVC pipe.
Yeah. I was leaning
more towards the floss.
but I guess you could
ingest. you know.
smaller parts of the
PVC pipe over time.
You know. like
have a time limit.
Right?
Sure.
[HORN HONKING]
[DOWN-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYING]
What if we're supposed
to suffer here?
What if that's the point?
Well. then that's bullshit.
I'll do it.
For him.
For us.
No.
It should be me.
[ENGINE IDLING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[ENGINE STOPS]
Day!
[DOOR CLOSES]
[KEYS JINGLING]
I'm sorry. man.
I'm sorry.
Give me the keys.
James-- I need you to give up.
OK?
I need you to give up. man.
You are torturing
yourself for an answer
that just doesn't exist. OK?
You are the reason that
you're suffering here now.
The engine's still hot.
It might still turn back on.
So just-- just give me the keys.
No.
We can't keep doing
this to ourselves.
You can't keep doing
this to yourself. OK?
We won't let you.
I didn't do this to myself.
I didn't put myself here.
Yeah.
Yeah. we're here too. James.
We lost everything too.
We are here too.
The only difference is that
we've been trying to accept it.
Because this life
is easy for you!
Because you're both
OK just sitting around
and doing fucking nothing.
You're both OK just
being victims here!
It's over. man.
It's done.
James!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Stop!
James!
Fucking stop!
James. get the fuck off of him!
James. let him go!
Stop!
James. fucking stop!
He can't fucking breathe!
Fisher. let go!
[KEYS JINGLE]
[ENGINE CRANKING]
Oh.
Oh. it was a test.
It was a test.
Oh. my God. it was fucking test.
It was a fucking test!
Oh. my God.
That was it.
James. there is no test.
So then just this?
Just here?
Forever!
I had hope. Day!
You have no idea what any
of this could have meant!
James. it doesn't
fucking mean anything.
OK?
There is no reason.
It just happened.
What the fuck do you
know about reason?
You were going to kill yourself!
Come on.
[ENGINE CRANKING]
Fucking. please start.
Please start.
Look. I will do anything.
Who the fuck are you talking to?
Come on.
Turn.
Fuck.
[CRANKING CONTINUES]
I will do it.
Just please. please!
Please start!
Fuck!
Just turn it on!
[CRANKING CONTINUES]
Please start!
[SCREAMS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
11:20.
Why is the road
setting a forest?
Why not an endless staircase?
[SNIFFS]
Over.
Hey. what is this?
What is this?
What's going on?
Hey.
Hey. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
[RAIN PATTERING]
Oh. this is good.
This is new.
Yeah.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Wait.
Wait. is this bad?
Hang on.
This is bad?
This is bad.
Please?
Wait. please tell me.
Please tell me.
What is this?
What the fuck is this!
Wait!
Please. please!
We can talk about this.
Fuck!
Oh. fuck!
Fuck. fuck!
It's because I left them. right?
Oh. God!
Shit!
[RAIN PATTERING]
[PATTERING SLOWS]
[PATTERING STOPS]
[MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC CRESCENDOS]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[INSECT BUZZING]
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
[ENGINE IDLING]
[SOBBING]
Fuck.
[CRYING] It's really good.
[SIGHS]
[SCREAMING]
All right. I'm coming.
[MID TEMPO POP MUSIC PLAYING
SOFTLY]
[DOWN-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS]
Hey. can I ask you a question?
Who would win in a fight--
50 hawks or a dude with a gun?
Probably the--
probably the hawks.
There's like 50 of them.
You think so?
Yeah.
Hm.
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WIND BLOWING]
[MID-TEMPO POP MUSIC PLAYS]
(SINGING) So. it's on
The feeling's gone and moving
Time is only mine to steal
Working on what is real
Found my song
Sang it wrong. no fooling
Warming up to all my chills
Thinking I'm over the hill
Tell me not to dwell
'cause I don't feel
like no one else. oh.
Why can't I feel like
there's something wrong?
there's something gone?
Wait. hold on
The sun has yet to dawn upon me
Reading everything I read
Know it's all in my head
The pressure's on
The feeling comes and slowly
Everyone is still
Thinking I'm over the hill
Tell me not to dwell
'cause I don't feel
like no one else. oh
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org